GONZALO BOSCHIN

INDUSTRIAL ENGINEER



ABOUT ME

I am a 28-year-old industrial engineer with three years of experience in the Big Data field. I consider myself proactive, outgoing, and equipped with excellent interpersonal skills. My curiosity and eagerness for continuous learning keep me up to date in the exciting world of technology. I am focused on acquiring strong technical expertise to lead projects and contribute to the technological transformation of companies.

EDUCATION

UTN - FRSR

Industrial Engineer 2016 - 2024

SKILLS

- · Programming languages
 - o Python
 - Linux/Unix
- Database:
 - · Hive SQL
- Visualization
 - o Power BI
 - Grafana
- Big Data tools:
 - Control-M
 - o Spark
 - Hadoop

LANGUAGES

- Español (NATIVO)
- Inglés (AVANZADO)

CONTACT

- boschingon@gmail.com
- (+54) 260-4593795
- Mendoza, Argentina

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Data Engineer SSR. / Functional Analyst

Telefónica - Oct 2023 - Currently

Responsible for the implementation, maintenance, and support of data processing workflows for large volumes of data in the production area, primarily focused on historical storage in Hadoop.

Tools: Python, SQL, Linux, Bash, Unix, Control-M, Spark, Tickets on Remedy

Data Engineer Jr.

NTT Data - Jan 2022 - Sep 2023

Development, implementation and maintenance of data pipelines, mainly for companies related to Oil & Gas. Group work under agile methodologies, estimation of efforts with the client, work reporting with PL and solution design.

Tools: Python, SQL, Cloudera, Apache Nifi, Spark, Scrum

Virtual Programming Environment Tutor

INTI - Oct 2022 - May 2023

I was part of a team of tutors for the National Institute of Industrial Technology, where we guided students on the platform, personally tracked their progress, and provided support within the framework of the #SeProgramar course.

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

- Diploma program in Python oriented to Machine Learning UTN FRSR
- Diploma program in blockchain y DeFi UTN FRBA
- Certification AZ-900 Azure Fundamentals Microsoft Learn
- Certification DP-900 Azure Data Fundamentals Microsoft Learn
- Certification AI-900 Azure AI Fundamentals Microsoft Learn